when it comes to critical illness
Insurance knowing the proper medical
definitions is
essential well the major critical
illnesses are those that are potentially
lifethreatening
[Music]
major critical
illness uh the threat to life is uh
almost real or almost immediate no the
minor CR itical illnesses if you will
notice the list are
mostly procedures which will
prevent progression to the major
critical illness you have different
procedures there and of course the a
mentioning uh it was also mentioned that
uh uh early cancers are considered as
minor critical illnesses aside from
knowing the proper medical terms it's
also imperative to review one's policy
care carefully uh most important thing
about claiming for critical illness the
client should be able to gather all the
medical
information uh specifically pathology
reports the diagnosis of their doctors
the hospital records so that there will
be no problems uh when they claim for a
critical illness benefit that is why it
is not the uh advisor's uh
responsibility anymore to make sure that
the documents submitted are correct
these will be reviewed by our claims
analysts and if there are any
deficiencies or questions about the
medical document submitted then they
refer to us here at the medical
Department critical illness
Insurance ask yourself are you covered
when life altering critical illness hits
you will your financial Heth still be on
track if you need to spend as much as a
million peses for your hospital
expenses critical illness insurance is
designed to pay the expenses associated
with life altering
illnesses so you can focus on getting
well and not on your finances to know
more about Sun life's health and
exellence insurance products talk to a
sunlife adviser
today or visit sunlife.com pH
[Music]
shine on Shine On